[music]
Another day of
what's wrong with
[music]
why did it happen like this
until the last argument.  [music]
Maybe because we don't have [music]
power yet
but it's impossible for me to hurt you
and not [music] the cleanest to
serve you.
You are my true [music]
actually [music] my intention to
leave you.
But [music] is hindered by the strong feeling of
love I have for [music]
.
[music]
dare
while you and I [music] are not always
in line
[music] the possibility of rushing
together
[music] stopping here there is no way
U can let go
[music]
your love is tightly attached to me.  [music]
forever
[music]
actually
my intention is to
prioritize [music] you
and I am hindered by
my love.  [music]
I have to give up
all my life.
[music] It's
too much for
me to [music] remind
you
too much.  [music]
This feeling cannot [music] change.
I don't want all that to
happen.  [music]
Actually my intention is to leave
[music]
you.
But
your love is strong.  [music]
beat [music] all my life
in
true anger [music]
that I could leave you
but the light [music] by the strength of my love
overcomes
My strength [music] is
too heavy.
[music]
My self is a
vase.
[music]
[music] [music
] [music] [music]
[music]
e